Eight arms, endless mind games. In Ink
Tensions, you play as rival octopuses
secretly placing cards to outthink your
opponents and claim the best food. Each
round, everyone plays seven cards
building arms towards food piles. Some
cards hunt, some hide, and some bring
chaos, all played face down. But nothing
is safe. Sharks can wipe out hunts while
clever plays slip through untouched.
Then every arm is revealed one card at a
time, creating tense, dramatic moments
as food is claimed or lost. Use one-time
octobility powers and quick punch
actions to disrupt plans in real time.
After several rounds, the most food
points wins. Stay one move ahead or go
hungry in Ink Tensions.